Rufaida Jumaa



Rufaida Jumaa

Address

3400, Hillerød, Danmark



+45 20710141



E-mail



GitHub



LinkedIn



Online portfolio

SKILLS

HTML/CSS

JavaScript(ES6)

NodeJS

MySQL

React

Git

Sitecore

Umbraco

Danish driving license

LANGUAGES

Arabic (Mother tongue)

Danish (Fluent for daily use level)

English (Professional level)

French (Basic understanding)

PROFILE

I am an ambitious and curious Web Developer with an Information Technology Engineering background. Since I moved to Denmark, back in 2017, I have learned 2 languages, English and Danish, studied Web Development intensively then joined Kruso as a web developer. I have had a break in my career because I became a mother for the second time.

After that, I refreshed my skills at HackYourFuture then I started an internship at Asosio to develop my skills with React and Web development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer - Asosio

12/2020 - Current - Copenhagen/ Denmark

Web Developer internship working with backend & frontend development tasks working mainly with React.JS(Next.js).

Web Developer - HackYourFuture

04/2020 - 10/2020 - Copenhagen/ Denmark

- . Web Developer internship to refresh my skills with JavaScript, Node.js,DB and React.
- . Refresh React skills and learn React hooks with an Online Course React ($\underline{\text{Scrimba}}).$
- . Designed and developed Arabi Food restaurant website using React.
- . Created my online portfolio using React.

Front-end Developer - KRUSO A/S

09/2018 - 11/2018 - Copenhagen/ Denmark

Frontend Developer working mainly with Umbraco, Sitecore, HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Web Developer - KRUSO A/S

02/2018 - 08/2018 - Copenhagen/ Denmark

Web Developer internship working with frontend & backend development tasks within different departments of the company.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development bootcamp - HackYourFuture

05/2017 - 14/1/2018 - Copenhagen/ Denmark

Full Stack Web Development bootcamp, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, MySQL, Express, React, GIT.

Bachelor of Information Technology Engineering - Damascus University 09/2011 - 11/2016 - Damascus/ Syria

- . Bachelor of Information Technology Engineering Computer Systems and Networks
- . 5 year education, Received Bachelor of Science, GPA (73.64)
- . (Equivalent to the Danish "professions-bachelor som diplomingeniør IT")

Secondary Education (Scientific Section) - Syrian Ministry Of Education 2010 – 08/2011 - Damascus/ Syria

Focus on Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry and Natural Sciences, Arabic, English and French, GPA (95.83).

VOLUNTEER WORK

- . I recently joined Matar Project to give the blind the opportunity to learn and study.
- . I have joined HackYourFuture community again to give back, I support the open office, mentoring in git classes, helping with feedback for application process and interviewing applicants and to give feedback for homework.
- Teacher / tutor children 6-13 years old Private
 Mathematics, Physics, IT, Chemistry, Biology and Arabic.